William Bentley Papers MS009
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Sermons, 1783 -- 1819; MS009.001; 10.45 Linear Feet
  - Sermon 328 -- Job XIII. 26, MS009.001.003.00017 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 329 -- II Timothy III. 12, MS009.001.003.00018 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 330 -- II Thessalonians III. 13, MS009.001.003.00019 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 331 -- Psalm XXXIX. 9, MS009.001.003.00020 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 332 -- Philippians II. 6-11, MS009.001.003.00021 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 333 -- Haggai I. 5, 6, MS009.001.003.00022 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 334 -- Revelation XII. 12, MS009.001.003.00023 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 335 -- I Corinthians IV. 5, MS009.001.003.00024 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 336 -- Mathew VII. 6, MS009.001.003.00025 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 337 -- Genesis XVIII. 18, 19, MS009.001.003.00026 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 338 -- Ecclesiastes VII. 29, MS009.001.003.00027 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 339 -- I Corinthians V. 11, MS009.001.003.00028 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 340 -- Mark IX. 24, MS009.001.003.00029 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 341 -- II Samuel XVI. 11, MS009.001.003.00030 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 342 -- Ephesians VI. 13, MS009.001.003.00031 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 343 -- Jonah I. 6, MS009.001.003.00032 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 344 -- II Kings VI. 5, MS009.001.003.00033 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 345 -- Numbers XVI. 13, MS009.001.003.00034 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 346 -- Hebrews II. 10, MS009.001.003.00035 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 347 -- Mathew V. 17, 18, 19, 20, MS009.001.003.00036 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 348 -- Luke XI. 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, MS009.001.003.00037 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 349 -- I Corinthians X. 23, 24, MS009.001.003.00038 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 350 -- Psalm LXXI. 18, MS009.001.003.00039 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 351 -- Acts IV. 12, MS009.001.003.00040 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 352 -- Mathew VII. 12, MS009.001.003.00041 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 353 -- Psalm I. 1, 2, MS009.001.003.00042 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 354 -- I Samuel XV. 32, MS009.001.003.00043 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 355 -- I Kings XVIII. 28, MS009.001.003.00044 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 356 -- Acts XXIV. 25, MS009.001.003.00045 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 357 -- Romans XIII. 7, MS009.001.003.00046 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 358 -- Psalm XXXVII. 8, MS009.001.003.00047 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 359 -- Habakkuk II. 3, 4, MS009.001.003.00048 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 360 -- Mathew IV. 23, MS009.001.003.00049 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 361 -- Acts XXVI. 28, MS009.001.003.00050 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 362 -- John XI. 7-10, MS009.001.003.00051 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 363 -- Isaiah XLIX. 4, MS009.001.003.00052 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 364 -- Ephesians VII. 28, MS009.001.003.00053 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 365 -- Hebrews VI. 11, MS009.001.003.00054 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 367 -- Acts XXVII. 20, MS009.001.003.00055 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 368 -- Romans II. 6, 7, MS009.001.003.00056 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 369 -- Isaiah XXI. 11, MS009.001.003.00057 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 370 -- I Corinthians V. 10, MS009.001.003.00058 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 371 -- Proverbs XXX. 32, MS009.001.003.00059 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 372 -- Luke IX. 23, MS009.001.003.00060 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 373 -- Jeremiah XVII. 9, MS009.001.003.00061 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 374 -- II Timothy II. 14, 15, 16, MS009.001.003.00062 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 375 -- Romans XII. 16, MS009.001.003.00063 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 376 -- I Corinthians XIV. 15, MS009.001.003.00064 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 377 -- Ecclesiastes V. 2, MS009.001.003.00065 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 378 -- Romans XIV. 13, MS009.001.003.00066 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 379 -- I Timothy I. 5, 6, 7, MS009.001.003.00067 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 380 -- Ecclesiastes VII. 1, MS009.001.003.00068 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 381 -- Acts XIX. 2, MS009.001.003.00069 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 382 -- Proverbs XIX. 19, MS009.001.003.00070 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 383 -- II Corinthians IX. 13, MS009.001.003.00071 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 384 -- II Chronicles I. 7-10, MS009.001.003.00072 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 385 -- John IV. 21, MS009.001.003.00073 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 386 -- Proverbs XXIV. 16, MS009.001.003.00074 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 387 -- I Thessalonians II. 11, 12, 13, MS009.001.003.00075 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 388 -- Psalm CXIX. 32, MS009.001.003.00076 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 389 -- Ecclesiastes VII. 16, 7, MS009.001.003.00077 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 390 -- Genesis L. 19, 20, MS009.001.003.00078 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 391 -- Proverbs XXIX. 1, MS009.001.003.00079 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 392 -- I Samuel II. 7, MS009.001.003.00080 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 393 -- II Timothy II. 3, MS009.001.003.00081 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 394 -- Proverbs XVI. 31, MS009.001.003.00082 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 395 -- I Kings XIX. 13-48, MS009.001.003.00083 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 396 -- Philippians IV. 13, MS009.001.003.00084 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 397 -- Acts XVII. 18, 19, 20, 21, MS009.001.003.00085 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 398 -- I Timothy I. 13, MS009.001.003.00086 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 399 -- Mark IX. 50, MS009.001.003.00087 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 400 -- Genesis XVI. 12, MS009.001.003.00088 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 401 -- Ecclesiastes V. 3, MS009.001.003.00089 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 402 -- Job VII. 1, MS009.001.003.00090 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 403 -- Colossians III. 8, MS009.001.003.00091 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 404 -- II Corinthians I. 24, MS009.001.003.00092 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 405 -- Psalm XC. 10, MS009.001.003.00093 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 406 -- Mathew VI. 13, MS009.001.003.00094 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 407 -- Genesis XXI. 10, MS009.001.003.00095 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 408 -- Psalm XV. 4, MS009.001.003.00096 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 410 -- Deuteronomy XXIX. 19, MS009.001.003.00097 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 411 -- John XIII. 18, MS009.001.003.00098 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 412 -- Isaiah LIV. 13, MS009.001.003.00099 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 413 -- II Corinthians I. 11, 12, MS009.001.003.00100 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 414 -- Revelations XVI. 15, MS009.001.003.00101 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 415 -- Acts X. 26, MS009.001.003.00102 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 416 -- Deuteronomy VIII. 10, MS009.001.003.00103 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 417 -- I Corinthians IX. 22, MS009.001.003.00104 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 418 -- Luke VIII. 49, MS009.001.003.00105 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 419 -- Isaiah LXVI. 8, MS009.001.003.00106 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 420 -- John XVII. 3, MS009.001.003.00107 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 422 -- Philippians IV. 5, MS009.001.003.00108 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 423 -- Ecclesiastes III. 7, MS009.001.003.00109 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 424 -- I Corinthians XVI. 2, MS009.001.003.00110 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 425 -- Proverbs XXV. 9, 10, MS009.001.003.00111 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 426 -- John IV. 20, MS009.001.003.00112 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 427 -- Proverbs XXVII. 8, MS009.001.003.00113 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 428 -- Romans II. 13, 14, 15, MS009.001.003.00114 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 429 -- Hebrews IV. 15, MS009.001.003.00115 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 430 -- Proverbs XIV. 34, MS009.001.003.00116 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 431 -- Acts XI. 26, MS009.001.003.00117 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 432 -- Romans I. 25, MS009.001.003.00118 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 433 -- Proverbs XVII. 6, MS009.001.003.00119 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 435 -- Numbers VI. 24, 25, 26, MS009.001.003.00120 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 436 -- John XXI. 15, MS009.001.003.00121 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 437 -- Psalm XL. 1, MS009.001.003.00122 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 438 -- Deuteronomy V. 16, MS009.001.003.00123 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 439 -- I Peter III. 16, MS009.001.003.00124 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 440 -- Job XVII. 14, MS009.001.003.00125 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 441 -- Acts XIII. 15, MS009.001.003.00126 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 442 -- John XVI. 26, 27, 28, 29, MS009.001.003.00127 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 443 -- Mathew IX. 9, MS009.001.003.00128 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 444 -- Luke VII. 31-35, MS009.001.003.00129 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 445 -- Job XVI. 21, 22, MS009.001.003.00130 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 446 -- Psalm CXI. 1, 2, 3, MS009.001.003.00131 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 447 -- Titus II. 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, MS009.001.003.00132 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 448 -- Joshua XXIV. 31, MS009.001.003.00133 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 449 -- Ezekiel XVI. 7, MS009.001.003.00134 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 450 -- II Corinthians XIII. 11, MS009.001.003.00135 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 460 -- I Corinthians II. 13, MS009.001.003.00136 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 461 -- Zechariah VIII. 4, MS009.001.003.00137 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 462 -- Genesis XLIX. 22-26, MS009.001.003.00138 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 463 -- Job V. 7, MS009.001.003.00139 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 464 -- Proverbs XXXI. 29, 30, MS009.001.003.00140 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 465 -- Mark I. 3, MS009.001.003.00141 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 483 -- Acts II. 39, MS009.001.003.00142 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 484 -- Exodus I. 7, MS009.001.003.00143 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 485 -- Luke II. 25, MS009.001.003.00144 (Box 3)
  - Sermon 486 -- Proverbs xxiv. 30,31,32,33,34, MS009.001.004.00001 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 484 -- Hosea vi. 4, MS009.001.004.00002 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 488 -- Luke xvi. 3, MS009.001.004.00003 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 489 -- Jeremiah ii. 25, MS009.001.004.00004 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 490 -- Genesis v. 27, MS009.001.004.00005 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 491 -- Psalm LV. 12,13, MS009.001.004.00006 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 492 -- I Kings xix. 4, MS009.001.004.00007 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 493 -- Mathew vi. 7,8, MS009.001.004.00008 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 494 -- II Corinthians ii. 13, MS009.001.004.00009 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 495 -- I Corinthians i. 22,23,24, MS009.001.004.00010 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 496 -- I Samuel i. 13, MS009.001.004.00011 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 498 -- Ecclesiastes xii. 5, MS009.001.004.00012 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 499 -- II Kings iv. 19, MS009.001.004.00013 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 500 -- I Corinthians vii. 20, MS009.001.004.00014 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 501 -- Luke vi. 39, MS009.001.004.00015 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 502 -- John vi. 70, MS009.001.004.00016 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 503 -- Cantiles iv. 16, MS009.001.004.00017 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 504 -- Judges xi. 39, MS009.001.004.00018 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 505 -- I Corinthians iv. 7, MS009.001.004.00019 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 506 -- II Thessalonians ii. 15, MS009.001.004.00020 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 507 -- I Timothy v. 3, MS009.001.004.00021 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 508 -- Mathew ix. 36, MS009.001.004.00022 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 509 -- Isaiah LV.ii., MS009.001.004.00023 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 510 -- Psalm xxxvii. 37, MS009.001.004.00024 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 511 -- Ruth ii. 14, MS009.001.004.00025 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 512 -- Proverbs vi. 20,21,22,23, MS009.001.004.00026 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 513 -- Jeremiah xxix. 7, MS009.001.004.00027 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 514 -- II Kings iv. 9,10, MS009.001.004.00028 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 516 -- I Corinthians ii. 14, MS009.001.004.00029 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 517 -- Ezeckiel xiv. 14, MS009.001.004.00030 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 518 -- Psalm xxxviii. 6-11, MS009.001.004.00031 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 519 -- I Timothy iv.1, MS009.001.004.00032 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 520 -- Job xxxi. 29,30, MS009.001.004.00033 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 521 -- Lamentations v.15, MS009.001.004.00034 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 522 -- Philippians ii. 27, MS009.001.004.00035 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 523 -- Mark viii. 27, MS009.001.004.00036 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 524 -- Job xiii. 15, MS009.001.004.00037 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 525 -- Proverbs i. 5, MS009.001.004.00038 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 526 -- I Corinthians vii. 15, MS009.001.004.00039 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 527 -- Job ix. 12, MS009.001.004.00040 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 528 -- John xiii. 34, MS009.001.004.00041 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 529 -- Luke xvii. 7, MS009.001.004.00042 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 530 -- Revelation ii. 9, MS009.001.004.00043 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 531 -- Daniel vi. 8, MS009.001.004.00044 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 532 -- Acts iii. 6, MS009.001.004.00045 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 533 -- Hosea xiii. 1, MS009.001.004.00046 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 534 -- Proverbs xvi. 33, MS009.001.004.00047 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 535 -- Galations iv. 19, MS009.001.004.00048 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 536 -- Ephesians v. 4, MS009.001.004.00049 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 537 -- Acts xxv. 12, MS009.001.004.00050 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 538 -- John xix. 26,27, MS009.001.004.00051 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 539 -- Psalm cxxvi. 3, MS009.001.004.00052 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 540 -- Ezekiel xviii. 26, MS009.001.004.00053 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 541 -- Proverbs xx. 25, MS009.001.004.00054 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 542 -- John xxi. 18, MS009.001.004.00055 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 543 -- Luke xi. 42, MS009.001.004.00056 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 544 -- Psalm C1. 1.2., MS009.001.004.00057 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 545 -- Hosea viii. 2, MS009.001.004.00058 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 546 -- Acts xi. 24, MS009.001.004.00059 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 547 -- John xiii. 27,28, MS009.001.004.00060 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 548 -- Proverbs xxx. 15, MS009.001.004.00061 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 549 -- Galatians vi. 3, MS009.001.004.00062 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 550 -- Psalm LXXXII. 6,7, MS009.001.004.00063 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 551 -- John vii. 10,11,12, MS009.001.004.00064 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 552 -- John xvii.12, MS009.001.004.00065 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 553 -- Acts xviii. 27, MS009.001.004.00066 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 554 -- Acts xiv. 11, MS009.001.004.00067 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 555 -- Colossians iv. 16, MS009.001.004.00068 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 556 -- Deuteronomy xxxii. 17, MS009.001.004.00069 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 557 -- Luke xi. 45, MS009.001.004.00070 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 558 -- Job xix. 21, MS009.001.004.00071 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 559 -- I Kings xi. 34, MS009.001.004.00072 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 560 -- Psalm cxxvii. 3,4,5, MS009.001.004.00073 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 561 -- Acts xvii. 5-9, MS009.001.004.00074 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 562 -- Luke vi. 35, MS009.001.004.00075 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 563 -- I Samuel xx. 42, MS009.001.004.00076 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 564 -- Acts xxiv. 26, MS009.001.004.00077 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 565 -- Proverbs xvi. 21, MS009.001.004.00078 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 566 -- Job i. 4,5, MS009.001.004.00079 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 567 -- Acts xxvi. 8, MS009.001.004.00080 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 568 -- Mathew xxiv. 29, MS009.001.004.00081 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 570 -- Acts xx. 35, MS009.001.004.00082 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 571 -- Joel ii. 13, MS009.001.004.00083 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 572 -- Isaiah LXI. 3, MS009.001.004.00084 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 573 -- Philippians iv. 17, MS009.001.004.00085 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 574 -- Luke ii. 36,37,38, MS009.001.004.00086 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 575 -- Psalm cxix. 60, MS009.001.004.00087 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 576 -- II Peter ii. 1, MS009.001.004.00088 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 577 -- II Peter ii. 9, MS009.001.004.00089 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 580 -- Job xi. 17, MS009.001.004.00090 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 581 -- Isaiah xxviii. 10, MS009.001.004.00091 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 582 -- Hosea x. 12, MS009.001.004.00092 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 583 -- Hosea iv. 6, MS009.001.004.00093 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 584 -- Ester iv. 16, MS009.001.004.00094 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 585 -- John iii. 26, MS009.001.004.00095 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 586 -- Hebrews xii. 3, MS009.001.004.00096 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 587 -- Psalm ciii. 15,16, MS009.001.004.00097 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 588 -- Haggai i. 2, MS009.001.004.00098 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 589 -- James iii. 6, MS009.001.004.00099 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 590 -- Acts ix. 13, MS009.001.004.00100 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 591 -- Psalm xxxix. 7, MS009.001.004.00101 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 592 -- Samuel xx. 3, MS009.001.004.00102 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 593 -- Romans vii. 15,16, MS009.001.004.00103 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 594 -- Genesis xxiii. 4, MS009.001.004.00104 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 595 -- Psalm cxxvi. 6, MS009.001.004.00105 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 596 -- Ephesians iv. 15, MS009.001.004.00106 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 597 -- II Timothy iv. 1,2,3,4,5, MS009.001.004.00107 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 598 -- II Peter i. 13, MS009.001.004.00108 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 599 -- Colossians iii. 22,2,3,24,25, MS009.001.004.00109 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 600 -- Luke iv. 41, MS009.001.004.00110 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 601 -- I Kings xxi. 5,6,7, MS009.001.004.00111 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 602 -- Luke xiv. 23, MS009.001.004.00112 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 603 -- Acts xii. 13,14, MS009.001.004.00113 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 604 -- Job vii. 7, MS009.001.004.00114 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 605 -- Psalm x. 6, MS009.001.004.00115 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 606 -- Leviticus xix. 30, MS009.001.004.00116 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 607 -- Jeremiah xxxiii. 11, MS009.001.004.00117 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 608 -- II Corinthians ii. 14-17, MS009.001.004.00118 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 609 -- John ix. 40, MS009.001.004.00119 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 610 -- Joshua xxiii. 11, MS009.001.004.00120 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 611 -- Romans xvi. 2, MS009.001.004.00121 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 612 -- Luke vii. 4,5, MS009.001.004.00122 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 613 -- Job ix. 21,22,23, MS009.001.004.00123 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 614 -- I Peter iii. 18, MS009.001.004.00124 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 615 -- Luke iii. 10,11, MS009.001.004.00125 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 616 -- Revelation iii. 11, MS009.001.004.00126 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 617 -- Acts xxviii. 4,5, MS009.001.004.00127 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 618 -- Luke xxi. 36, 37, 38, MS009.001.004.00128 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 619 -- Job vii. 3,4, MS009.001.004.00129 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 620 -- Mathew vi. 11, MS009.001.004.00130 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 621 -- II Thessalonians iii. 11,12, MS009.001.004.00131 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 622 -- I Peter i.13, MS009.001.004.00132 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 623 -- II Corinthians x. 12, MS009.001.004.00133 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 624 -- Luke vii. 25, MS009.001.004.00134 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 625 -- II Peter iii. 8, MS009.001.004.00135 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 626 -- Romans i. 19, MS009.001.004.00136 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 627 -- I Samuel ix. 27, MS009.001.004.00137 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 628 -- Exodus xxxii. 24, MS009.001.004.00138 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 629 -- Ecclesiastes i. 2, MS009.001.004.00139 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 630 -- Isaiah xxxviii. 19 and Records of Town to 1793, MS009.001.004.00140 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 631 -- Proverbs i. 10, MS009.001.004.00141 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 632 -- I Peter i. 11, MS009.001.004.00142 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 633 -- Proverbs iv. 10-15, MS009.001.004.00143 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 634 -- Ecclesiates viii. 5, MS009.001.004.00144 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 635 -- Job ix. 6, MS009.001.004.00145 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 636 -- Hosea i. 10, MS009.001.004.00146 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 637 -- Luke xix. 37, MS009.001.004.00147 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 638 -- I Thessalonians v. 22, MS009.001.004.00148 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 641 -- Luke xv. 31, MS009.001.004.00149 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 642 -- Luke xii. 1, MS009.001.004.00150 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 643 -- Judges xiii. 8, MS009.001.004.00151 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 644 -- Luke ix. 9, MS009.001.004.00152 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 645 -- I Kings xix. 3, MS009.001.004.00153 (Box 4)
  - Sermon 646 -- Job vii. 7, MS009.001.005.00001 (Box 5)
  - Sermon 647 -- Psalm LXXI. 9, MS009.001.005.00002 (Box 5)
  - Sermon 648 -- Psalm LXVIII. 5, MS009.001.005.00003 (Box 5)
  - Sermon 649 -- Rev iii. 19, MS009.001.005.00004 (Box 5)
  - Sermon 650 -- Jeremiah ix. 23, 24, MS009.001.005.00005 (Box 5)
  - Sermon 651 -- Isaiah L. 10,11, MS009.001.005.00006 (Box 5)
  - Sermon 652 -- Exodus i. 10, MS009.001.005.00007 (Box 5)
  - Sermon 653 -- Proverbs xi. 2, MS009.001.005.00008 (Box 5)
  - Sermon 654 -- Numbers xi. 29, MS009.001.005.00009 (Box 5)
  - Sermon 655 -- Nehemiah iv. 6, MS009.001.005.00010 (Box 5)
  - Sermon 656 -- Judges xvi. 16, MS009.001.005.00011 (Box 5)
  - Sermon 657 -- Matthew xxvii. 25, MS009.001.005.00012 (Box 5)
  - Sermon 658 -- Revelation iii. 4, MS009.001.005.00013 (Box 5)
  - Sermon 659 -- Galatians vi. 4, MS009.001.005.00014 (Box 5)
  - Sermon 660 -- Acts xx. 24, MS009.001.005.00015 (Box 5)
  - Sermon 661 -- Galatians v. 19-23, MS009.001.005.00016 (Box 5)
  - Sermon 662 -- Ruth i. 8,9, MS009.001.005.00017 (Box 5)
  - Sermon 663 -- I Corinthians xv. 35, 36, MS009.001.005.00018 (Box 5)
  - Sermon 664 -- Amos v. 13, MS009.001.005.00019 (Box 5)
  - Sermon 665 -- Acts xxviii. 22, MS009.001.005.00020 (Box 5)
  - Sermon 666 -- Acts LXVI. 13, MS009.001.005.00021 (Box 5)
  - Sermon 667 -- I Timothy vi. 7, MS009.001.005.00022 (Box 5)
  - Sermon 668 -- Judges viii. 23, MS009.001.005.00023 (Box 5)
  - Sermon 671 -- II Chronicles xxx. 18, 19, MS009.001.005.00024 (Box 5)
  - Sermon 672 -- James iii. 10, MS009.001.005.00025 (Box 5)
  - Sermon 673 -- Psalm LXXXIX. 47, MS009.001.005.00026 (Box 5)
  - Sermon 674 -- Psalm cxxxix. 7, MS009.001.005.00027 (Box 5)
  - Sermon 675 -- Revelation v. 4, MS009.001.005.00028 (Box 5)
  - Sermon 676 -- Zechariah viii. 19, MS009.001.005.00029 (Box 5)
  - Sermon 677 -- Joshua ix. 3, 4, MS009.001.005.00030 (Box 5)
  - Sermon 678 -- Titus ii. 5, MS009.001.005.00031 (Box 5)
  - Sermon 679 -- Psalm x. 4, MS009.001.005.00032 (Box 5)
  - Sermon 680 -- Ephisians v. 3, MS009.001.005.00033 (Box 5)
  - Sermon 681 -- Matthew vi. 3, MS009.001.005.00034 (Box 5)
  - Sermon 682 -- II Timothy iv. 13, MS009.001.005.00035 (Box 5)
  - Sermon 683 -- Proverbs xxviii. 14, MS009.001.005.00036 (Box 5)
  - Sermon 684 -- Ephesians v. 13, MS009.001.005.00037 (Box 5)
  - Sermon 685 -- Acts viii. 27, MS009.001.005.00038 (Box 5)
  - Sermon 686 -- James iii. 5, MS009.001.005.00039 (Box 5)
  - Sermon 687 -- I Samuel xx. 7, MS009.001.005.00040 (Box 5)
  - Sermon 688 -- I Kings xviii. 12, MS009.001.005.00041 (Box 5)
  - Sermon 689 -- Isaiah ii. 4, MS009.001.006.00001 (Box 6)
  - Sermon 690 -- Proverbs xx. 24, MS009.001.006.00002 (Box 6)
  - Sermon 691 -- Philippians iii. 18, 19, MS009.001.006.00003 (Box 6)
  - Sermon 692 -- Luke xxiv. 21, MS009.001.006.00004 (Box 6)
  - Sermon 693 -- John v. 14, MS009.001.006.00005 (Box 6)
  - Sermon 694 -- Ephesians iv. 14, MS009.001.006.00006 (Box 6)
  - Sermon 695 -- Romans iii. 1, 2, MS009.001.006.00007 (Box 6)
  - Sermon 696 -- Philippians iii. 12, MS009.001.006.00008 (Box 6)
  - Sermon 697 -- Genesis XLII. 11, MS009.001.006.00009 (Box 6)
  - Sermon 698 -- Ezekiel xiv. 7, MS009.001.006.00010 (Box 6)
  - Sermon 699 -- Luke viii. 53, MS009.001.006.00011 (Box 6)
  - Sermon 700 -- John iii. 21, MS009.001.006.00012 (Box 6)
  - Sermon 701 -- Matthew xv. 16, MS009.001.006.00013 (Box 6)
  - Sermon 702 -- Proverbs xiii. 17, MS009.001.006.00014 (Box 6)
  - Sermon 703 -- John xii. 27, 28, MS009.001.006.00015 (Box 6)
  - Sermon 704 -- John xvi. 14, MS009.001.006.00016 (Box 6)
  - Sermon 705 -- Matthew xix. 17, MS009.001.006.00017 (Box 6)
  - Sermon 706 -- Hebrew vi. 1, MS009.001.006.00018 (Box 6)
  - Sermon 707 -- Romans viii. 25, MS009.001.006.00019 (Box 6)
  - Sermon 708 -- John viii. 28, MS009.001.006.00020 (Box 6)
  - Sermon 709 -- Proverbs iv. 1-9, MS009.001.006.00021 (Box 6)
  - Sermon 710 -- John xiii. 17, MS009.001.006.00022 (Box 6)
  - Sermons, 710-800, MS009.001.007 (Box 7)
  - Sermons, 801-900, MS009.001.008 (Box 8)
  - Sermons, 901-1000, MS009.001.009 (Box 9)
  - Sermons, 1001-1100, MS009.001.010 (Box 10)
  - Sermons, 1101-1203, MS009.001.011 (Box 11)
  - Bentley sermons and indices, 1783 -- 1819; MS009.001.012 (Box data_value_missing_e433e7be9b4d85ea289de84f60c6e308, Box 12)
    Contains handwritten catalogs/indices of Bentley's sermons, a notebook of sermons, a notebook of poems(?), a language notebook, loose pages and photocopies, and a typed catalog ("Sermons of Reverend William Bentley, 1759-1819" by Alan Seaburg, May 26, 1964) featuring the following note on the first page: "In 1866, Mrs. W. B. Fowle of Medfield, Massachusetts, presented to the Tufts University Library the manuscript sermons, devotional exercises and a few other items of the Reverend William Bentley. … The Tufts' manuscripts consist of over 1200 sermons. They are listed here as William Bentley arranged them and for each sermon is given the scripture text, the paging, and any appropriate notes and dates. The material is housed in the vault." Sermons were found in stacks that we should not have; others are missing; see notes in box.
    The notebook with handwritten sermons in the unprocessed box (largest notebook in box by cover size) is one of a series that Bentley kept during his life. The other notebooks in this series appear to be held at the American Antiquarian Society – finding aid for their Bentley papers: http://www.americanantiquarian.org/Findingaids/william_bentley.pdf